Guide to the Ruth Crawford Mitchell Papers, 1914-1980 UA.90.F12
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Nativity Study [RESTRICTED], 1926-1930; VI.
  - Foreign Students and the United States Immigration Laws; Ruth Crawford Mitchell, University of Pittsburgh, Pittsburgh, Pa., June, 1928, (University Revision) (Box 7, Folder 234)
  - Student Study 1928-29 (Box 7, Folder 235)
  - Nativity Statistics of Student Populations, 1928-29 (Box 7, Folder 236)
  - Original Tables: Student Study, 1928-29 (Box 7, Folder 237)
  - Foreign Born Student Lists: Student Study 1928-29 (Box 7, Folder 238)
  - Second Generation Student Lists: Student Study 1928-29 (Box 7, Folder 239)
  - Committee on Second Generation Students: Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 240)
  - Committee on Second Generation Students: Special Material 1928-29 (Box 7, Folder 241)
  - Committee on Second Generation Students: Annual Report 1929 (Box 7, Folder 242)
  - Third Annual Report, 1928-29 Nativity Study, Extra Copies (Box 7, Folder 243)
  - Complete Set of Tables, Student Study 1928-29 (Box 7, Folder 244)
  - Foreign Born Student Lists: Student Study 1927-28 (Box 7, Folder 245)
  - Second Generation Student Lists: Student Study 1927-28 (Box 7, Folder 247)
  - Committee on Second Generation Students: Minutes and Program, 1926-27 and Minutes and Program, 1927-28 (Box 7, Folder 248)
  - Cover Page, List of Tables, Definition of Terms and Tables, Student Study 1927-28 (Box 8, Folder 249)
  - Tables I-X, Student Study 1926-27 (Box 8, Folder 250)
  - Statistical Tables and General (Box 8, Folder 251)
  - Second Generation Material, Student Study 1926-27 (Box 8, Folder 252)
  - Second Generation College-Combined Final Tables (Box 8, Folder 253)
  - Second Generation - Gentile, The College (Box 8, Folder 254)
  - Second Generation - Jewish, The College (Box 8, Folder 255)
  - Foreign Born Students - College 1926 (Box 8, Folder 256)
  - Ellis, Miss - Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 257)
  - Ellis, Mabel - Report (Box 8, Folder 258)
  - Zemo, Peter - Second Generation Study, April 1928 (Box 8, Folder 259)
  - Wajert, Anthony - Second Generation Study, April 1928 (Box 8, Folder 260)
  - Squitieri, Gilbert - Second Generation Study, April 1928 (Box 8, Folder 261)
  - Rusiewicz, Leon - Second Generation Study, April 1928 (Box 8, Folder 262)
  - Hadden, Thomas - Second Generation Study, April 1928 (Box 8, Folder 263)
  - Kline, Louis J. - Second Generation Study, April 1928 (Box 8, Folder 264)
  - Minnis, John Hough - Second Generation Study, April 1928 (Box 8, Folder 265)
  - Reiter, Samuel - Second Generation Study, April 1928 (Box 8, Folder 266)
  - Wratney, Martha J. - Second Generation Study, April 1928 (Box 8, Folder 267)
  - Original Data - Student Study 1926-27 (Box 8, Folder 268)
  - Student Study - Beginnings 1925-26 (Box 8, Folder 269)
  - Final Report - Student Study 1926-27 (Box 8, Folder 270)
  - Miscellaneous - Student Study 1926-27 (Box 8, Folder 271)
  - Study of Foreign Students, University of Pittsburgh - 1925 (Box 8, Folder 272)
  - Second Generation Professional Schools - Non-English Speaking (Box 8, Folder 273)
  - Second Generation Professional Schools - English Speaking (Box 8, Folder 274)
  - Rice, Anna - Second Generation Study - April 1928 (Box 8, Folder 275)
  - Second Generation Student Clubs - Czechoslovakian Student Clubs (Box 8, Folder 276)
  - Second Generation Student Clubs - Hungarian Clubs (Box 8, Folder 277)
  - Write Up Material for Second Generation Student Study - Individual Cases - Photographs (Box 8, Folder 278)
  - Second Generation Study - Individual Case Stories (Box 8, Folder 279)
  - Nativity Study 1926-1929, Preliminary Finding, 3 Years (Box 8, Folder 280)
  - Committee on Second Generation Students - Study on Freshman Women (Box 8, Folder 281)
  - Second Generation Student Clubs - Polish Students Club (Box 8, Folder 282)
  - Second Generation Study - Plans Outlined for Study in Public Schools (Box 8, Folder 283)
  - Foreign Born and Second Generation Students at the U. of P. - 1933 - 5 Years, Preliminary Statement R.C.M. (Box 8, Folder 284)
  - Write Up Material for Second Generation Student Study - Psychological Interpretations (Box 8, Folder 285)
  - Write Up Material for Second Generation Student Study - Crime and Delinquency (Box 8, Folder 286)
  - Second Generation Study - Magazine Articles (Box 8, Folder 287)
  - Write Up Material for Second Generation Student Study -Second School Influence (Box 8, Folder 288)
  - Write Up Material for Second Generation Student Study - Second Generation in the General Community (Box 8, Folder 289)
  - Nativity Study - Preliminary Findings with Statistical Data, 4 years (Box 8, Folder 290)
  - R.C. Mitchell Faculty Papers (Box 9, Folder 291)
  - R.C. Mitchell Faculty Papers (Box 9, Folder 292)
  - Committee on Foreign Students Minutes 1927-28 (Box 9, Folder 293)
  - Student Nativity Study: Volume One (Box 9, Folder 294)
  - Student Nativity Study: Volume Two (Box 9, Folder 295)
  - Student Nativity Study: Volume Three (Box 9, Folder 296)
  - Card File Foreign Student Immigration Status (Box 10)
  - Card File Foreign Student Immigration Status
  - Index Cards